<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>network on Xiao.chen</title>
    <link>https://blog.wisekee.com/tags/network/</link>
    <description>Recent content in network on Xiao.chen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2020, Xiao.chen; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.wisekee.com/tags/network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Open source security tools for beginners</title>
      <link>https://blog.wisekee.com/post/opensource-security-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.wisekee.com/post/opensource-security-tools/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            ossim tcpdump tshark wireshark Nmap skipfish security onion snort zeek openvas,Greenbone Community Edition backbox kali platform penetration testing and security assessmen zeltser Threats with ATT&amp;amp;CK-based Analytics threat hunting tools canarytokens security tools and parse events for most products open source, cross platform web application firewall (WAF) Coraza is a golang enterprise-grade Web Application Firewall framework About A collection of awesome framework, libraries, learning tutorials, videos, webcasts, technical resources and cool stuff about Security Orchestration, Automation and Response (SOAR).
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forward the traffic to internal server through iptables rule use bastion server</title>
      <link>https://blog.wisekee.com/post/iptables-forward-traffic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.wisekee.com/post/iptables-forward-traffic/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Sometimes we have access internal service or server in local network,needs through external bastion server bridge to.
1# The traffic forward to internal environment through bastion iptables rule diagram 2 3# local or office ------&amp;gt; bastion machine ----------&amp;gt; internal server 4# local access bastion-public-ip:8888 -----&amp;gt; bastion iptables rules ----&amp;gt; internal server:80 5 6# display iptalbes nat rules 7iptables -t nat -L 8 9# add prepostrouting rule to chain 10iptables -t nat -A PREROUTING -p tcp -m tcp --dport 8899 -j DNAT --to-destination 192.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS networking security enhance</title>
      <link>https://blog.wisekee.com/post/aws-network-secrutiy-enhance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.wisekee.com/post/aws-network-secrutiy-enhance/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Vpc network division According to the requirements of the product and the customer, the two services of the two types of subnets are isolated. For example, DBsubnet01 and DBsubnet02 are both internal private subnets and belong to different product segments. ​	The two major subnet types are the intranet and the extranet. The internal network goes to the NAT Gateway, and the external network goes to the Internet Gateway. Like: RDS, Redis, background services, etc.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
